Music
Thank you for watching
Thank you for watching!
Hello everyone!
I'm Takato Okura!
I am Takato Okura!
I am Daisaku Omitsu!
I am Jun Muto!
I'm Daisaku Ohkura!
Here it comes!
Nice to meet you, YouTube shoot!
Yes!
So, what are the three of us going to do this time?
What are you going to do?
The three of us.
Yes!
Let's shoot yellowtail!
Great!
And you two, by the way?
Actually, me and Jun, this year?
This year?
I don't really know why we decided to do it.
I don't know.
Why?
It was there.
There?
So we decided to take a picture to remember.
We took it together.
That's right.
That was my plan. We took it last year, right?
Was Kozo there?
Yes, yes, yes. Oh yes, yes, yes.
I'm going to make that mole bigger.
Yes, yes, yes, it's been two years or something, right?
Two years ago?
That long ago?
Since then...
That's why I'm here at Furyuu-san.
Yes!
I'm going to take some pictures of the sprit...
This is
Amazing!
It's right in front of me!
Wow!
They all look like they're going to leak.
Yes, they're all leaking.
This is nice.
Okay, let's see what Mr. Furyuu has in store for us.
I'd like to take a picture of this piemo.
I'd like to take some pictures of the swinging out.
Please take a picture of this.
It's going to be beautiful.
Yes, it will.
So...
They're in good order.
Moisture and moisture mixed together.
More moisture.
More moisture. More moisture?
I'm going to shoot for the ultimate moisture
Jun Mutou pushing
The desire to see Jun-kun
Jun Jun
So that's what this is about.
There's also the light.
Light, you mean.
It means there's also craftsmanship in it.
That's good. That's good.
By the way, each of these plinkies has its own characteristics.
Each one has its own characteristics. You said each one has its own characteristics.
You have characteristics.
Characteristics
In addition to pure greed leakage, there is a theme
Y2K
Y2K.
Two Y's, right?
Yup.
YO YO
K
Observer
I see. YO YO observer.
Then it's not called Piemo.
Y2K, it's what we call Heisei Sensation.
Heisei Sense
Heisei sensation
It's like a pudding of the Heisei era.
The background is shiny.
It's very leaky.
It leaks like that.
That's Heisei culture.
I see.
We take pictures of puddings, right?
We take pictures of pudding keys.
By all means.
We want to take a picture of all the observers who support us.
I want you to take a picture of us with all the observers who support us.
We want you to take a picture of us!
We want you to take a picture with us.
We can take some pictures of the pudding.
Yes, they can.
Each time, we can take a picture of the three of us together.
We'll decide the pose of the three of us.
And then we'll take pictures of the three of us, and we'll take pictures of the three of us.
We want observers to try to imitate our poses.
Poses.
Decorations and so on.
Oh, right. Oh, yeah.
It's a little bit like architecture, like the three of us.
That's what you mean.
Decorate it.
Something everyone can copy.
I can write.
I'd like to put it out there like this.
That's good.
How about decorations?
Decoration?
What happened when we took the picture together?
When we took the picture together...
I don't know. I don't know.
I was like, "This is fine.
It was safe.
Yeah, it was safe.
So it's like a heart.
Yes, yes.
I was trying to take the high road.
We were trying to take the high road.
But if we're going to make something that only the three of us can do...
I'd like to shoot something new.
That's right.
But time is running out soon after we sell out.
So it's better to think about it in advance while we still can.
I see.
That's what I'm talking about... short, good shots.
Something that doesn't take too long to put on quickly.
Like a good stamp.
I'd like to write one thing.
Do you have one?
Let's see, it's for each person.
I see.
If it's a corner, like a sunflower.
A sunflower.
I see.
Flowers and stuff.
I see... the features. I see... features.
Sunflowers. I'll draw you some sunflowers.
I'll draw a sunflower.
What's this?
A rose.
Oh, roses? That's nice.
What do you draw that's white?
Lilies.
How do you draw it?
I draw my own lilies.
It's in my head.
You draw it yourself.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Flowers...
This is for crafts.
Doodles of white animals...
White animal doodles.
Rabbits, white bears...
A polar bear.
Yeah, I like that.
I do that myself.
Yeah.
Like a polar bear.
A bear.
Shima Shima.
And then...
Oh, okay. Chicks. Chicks.
Oh, chickens.
Eggs, chicks, nibbles, I'm here.
Eggs, chicks, showers.
Eggs, chickens, nesting clusters.
Yes, sir.
How do you do it?
Certainly.
Let's decide on a few poses. Let's decide on a few poses.
That's only about five seconds.
But it's the Heisei era.
You didn't put Galpia in there?
No, I didn't.
Three.
Two.
One.
All right, everybody, right here.
Here... here's the focus.
All eyes are on this one.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God, that's great.
The expressions on their faces are so funny.
Expression is important.
The expression...
It's great.
That's great.
You're not a galsupi!
It's too cool.
Well, we're used to it.
I'd love to do one Gal-Pi.
It's Y2K, so to speak.
It's Y2K.
It's like...
It's very you.
You look like a lady.
Let's take a shot.
Urkila Greedy Monet.
Greedy Monet. That's a good one.
Oh, so this is a full-body shot.
They have full body shots, too.
You can choose the background.
This kind of background is very Heisei style.
It's sparkling. - You're right, a full body shot is not so easy.
Backgrounds.
Okay, let's pick one for each of you.
Okay. - No, this is the one. OK - no, this is it.
Oh, first of all, it's got nice sparkles.
Okay, let's, uh, let's find out.
Uh, oh, my gosh, uh...
If you're going for something animal, like this.
I like it, I like it. - Animal's good.
I'm off! - I'm so excited!
I'm off! - I'm so excited, I'm so excited!
Oh, here it comes!
Oh, there he is!
It's a hobe heart. - A hobe heart.
Oh, it's leaking so much!
Oh, no!  - Oh, no, no, no, no...
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. - Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. - Oh, yeah, yeah. Be careful.
Steady, steady. - Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
Oh, wow, thick. - It's gonna make you look so small.
Pretty and sleek. - Nice and sleek.
How do you like that?
What do you think? Like, super spiffy.
You look so cool.
Oh, sometime...
I was already conscious of my legs.
Me too, me too.
Good, good, good.
Oh, graffiti.
Doodles.
Okay, let's do two.
A lot.
I'm not going to tell you... but I found something good...
I've got a great one, Ozawa-san... on your finger...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
He said we have 2 minutes left
Yuri, yuri, yuri
Yuri, Yuri, Yuri...
Jun, you don't write, erase, write, erase, do you?
No, I'm just... I'm just trying to get this background to look right.
Oh, that's good. That's good.
It's nice. It's good, isn't it?
That's good. That's good.
Can I write a sunflower?
Sunflowers.
Yes, you can write yokozuna.
What are you going to write?
Brown.
Oh, my God, why not a butterfly?
Wait a minute, that's too big!
It's just a melon bread.
Wait a minute, wow!
Bonus time! It's stuck at 65!
Hey!
Bonus for life!
He's already given us a bonus!
It's a huge bonus!
I'll give it to you.
Baby course.
Yes, 20% complete!
Yes, yes, yes.
How's it going over there?
Oh, well, what about...?
Roses?
Babjoon. Babjoon.
Bab-joon.
Babu?
Oh, they're all Babs.
We're on the baby track.
Babu, Babu.
Oh, yeah.
Uh...
But you know what?
I think the hiragana might be Heisei.
Yes, that's true.
You have a really good point. Maybe...
I mean... Junmaa! Wow, here it comes!
Junmaa! Here it comes! Sequential! I'm here!
No, I'm embarrassed!
Yuri, I'm embarrassed
Yuri, I'm so embarrassed! Yuri, let's put it on.
Can we not do the tosaka or something? I'll do a tosakka.
Can I?
Wow, what's this?
It's got black edges, Jun.
Yeah.
My dark one already.
Hey, hey, where's my tosakas? Tosaka, Tosaka, Tosaka.
Just me. Here's my tosakas.
Here it is.
It's done. It's good, it's cute. It's good, it's good, it's good.
It's an egg.
And Takato is a chick.
Takato is a chick.
So fun, so fun, so fun, so fun!
Okay, yellow...
Look, I processed it for you. It's so Heisei.
I'll do the same for you, Jun.
What's this?
Okay, Y2K.
Y2K?
I'm pretty sure.
You like it? The T?
I think this one's better with the blue glitter.
üyori titacle
One.
Two.
Three.
Six.
I can't help it, I can't help it.
I'm sorry. I just saw it.
It's swampy, isn't it? Swampy, huh?
It's nice, isn't it?
Jun.
It's the easiest thing I've ever seen.
That's great!
Maybe we should take a picture together.
No.1, No.1, No.1
I'm so happy.
You're so good!
And do you have a flower called "Sheep"?
Flowers of flowers.
That's cute.
How fun, Mr. Hossaku!
It's fun, isn't it?
It's pretty time-consuming.
But it's nice to have bonus time.
Bonus time is what makes it all worth it.
It's because of the bonus time that the two of us can work together to decorate and make something nice.
That's true.
It's fun to paint in a hurry.
That's right.
What's that? Mr. Kotaku!
Would you like to see the others?
Shall we take a look?
There are so many.
There's so many!
Each one has its own charm.
This one's new.
It says "new" on it.
This is the newest one.
Let's take this one.
I'm attracted to the new ones.
I'm attracted to new.
It's got something written on it.
A moderately burning triple shot
This is the kind of thing you can take after you've taken
I can take them. I can take it.
It's more realistic.
You mean like that?
With all the backgrounds and stuff.
It's good because it burns in moderation.
There's a point, isn't there?
I like it. This is good. This is good. Let's try it.
Now that we've taken the time to shoot this photo shoot for My Palette, let's see.
So, let's take a picture with My Palette... and let's try some poses and words... like if it were us.
For example, TKJ...
Like TKJ, or the pose where she's saying, "I love myself because I'm the cause.
Observers... anyone can do it.
I'm an observer.
I'm observing you.
Okay, let's do that.
You can't make your face look pretty, so let's do it like this.
Okay, okay, like this.
Don't put it over your face.
Great, great.
I don't know about me.
I don't know.
We recently went on a spring tour.
They've been doing a lot of scoring sessions at release events.
I have a pose for one of them.
I have a pose like this.
This is the pose of the brothers of the new concept EP.
I want to take one of these poses.
It's a "what if" pose.
It's Silence.
I knew I needed to do this with Silence.
It's the memory that I'm the cause of all this.
I want you to do it.
Here we go.
Here.
You guys want to see this?
What's a urumi leak?
Well, I'm a little curious.
Oh, I see it! I saw it!Oh, I saw it! I saw it!
A great clear picture!
This is nice. I'm so happy.
Thank you very much.
Isn't this going to be see-through already? This one.
It's too transparent.
You can set the angle of view to portrait or landscape.
I do that a lot.
Horizontal is fine.
There's three of us.
Unusual.
Oh yeah, you can choose two flanks.
Selfie time.
Here it is.
Only at My Palette.
Yes, ma'am.
To leave it on the camera
Come on, let's go for cute!
Let's go for the Furumi leak!
I was in the middle earlier, so next...
Okay, Kousaku, let's go in the middle.
Oh, Jun, go this way!
I just did...
What?
I said, "It's about to start.
You scared me.
I'm so nervous.
Oh, stop it.
You're making me nervous.
We pause for observation
Oh, okay, okay.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Isn't this side really nice?
What was that again?
What what what what?
Science.
What if... If
Oh, Science.
No, no, no. Next time I'll do science. Next time I'll do science.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Locklearner.
Oh, here it comes!
Oh, wait, I can pick any light I want.
Uh, hey.
Pink. Takato's favorite color.
Okay, first of all, I want pink.
One more thing. One more thing.
There's one in pink.
Let's do this one, okay?
One. - What's the second one?
This one? A pretty color.
Natural?
One natural.
Cute.
This one's pink.
Yes? Yes?
It's cute.
I'm going for a piece.
There he is!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm in a soft mood.
Here it is. I think I'd rather pose.
I knew I told you, you're so transparent.
Beyond transparent, really amazing
Then transparency.
Can we max it out at 100% and turn it off?
I can turn it off?
Like I'm not here.
That's amazing. What's the point of taking a picture of that?
I wonder if it's possible to do this for yay-beans, which is so popular right now.
Wow!
It's all the rage right now.It's all the rage now.
Yebbey, bluebey...
I can do that.
I'm gonna do something I've always wanted to do.
I'll write it down next.
So you're going to do what Jun wanted to do.
A pen.
Write this in a circle.
Target like this.
Scope like this
I see.
That's what he's aiming for.
You can't miss what you're aiming for.
Quickly, quickly...
- Okay!  - You got it.
No, no, no, no. He's cute.
Observers.
You missed a guess.
It's cute. - It's cute.
It's so cute. - It's so cute. - It's so cute.
It's so cute! It's so good!
I don't know what to write.
I don't know what to write. - Shall I write, "Be quiet" or something? Here.
How's this? Oh, that's good.
Be quiet!
What if...
It's a little out of balance.
A little more this way.
You're the type of person who cares more about balance than you think.
Come on, come on, come on.
What do you think?
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
It's got a lot of horns in it.
Eggs, chicks, and antlers.
Demons, demon kings...
I'm going to kill a hero.
Then be quiet and I'll write it down.
Quietly. Quietly
Quiet.
Oh, that's good.
And be quiet.
Oh, good.
You guys can certainly be quiet now.
Oh, I'm starting to fill in the eggs.
Oh, no, I don't know what I'm going to do now.
It's done!
Aaaaahhh!
Oh, I'm so excited!
So much fun!
This is fun!
I think this is a masterpiece!
It's a masterpiece.
Yeah, I think I got it right the second time.
I'm getting better at posing.
I'm getting better at posing, and I have a wider variety of doodles.
Yes, I think so.
But one of them was a little too good.
You were good.
It was kind of difficult.
You're good.
No, I'm glad.
It's simple.
A bit far from pre
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
What?
They're here.
Oh, here it is.
Oh, my God!
It's here.
Yes, I mean...
It looks like this.
Isn't this selfie time so good?
Stylish, isn't it?
Yes, it's nice.Yeah, nice.
Suddenly it's so cool.
Yeah, it's so stylish, this selfie time.
What a cute photo and a cool photo.
You guys are really good at decorating.
Okay, here's a little bit of today's look.
Wow, they're having so much fun!
That's amazing.
I love it!
We're JKs on our day off, too.
We made it.
How about your favorite picture of the day?
It's Jun-san's favorite.
I'm always up for a good shot.
I know.
It's nice. I wonder why he thinks it's nice.
Just keep it down. Keep it down.
Yeah, it's good.
It's good. I think it's good.
I think it's good.
I think this is good. TKJ.
TKJ here. Great. The three of us. We're having fun.
Once again, the three of us took a picture together today. I'd like to go out with the other members for a while.
I'd like to go out with the other members and make more graffiti again.
I'd also like to tell you that observers who've seen our YouTube videos can see this pose.
If you can tell me something about it, I'll try it out next time.
And we'll have them take a picture of us, using our poses as a reference.
Please give it a try!
So, everyone, please try taking pictures with your good friends, family members, and various people.
I hope you'll try it out with your family and friends.
Thank you very much.